(Upbeat music playing)
No matter the distance, No matter how
years turn. Love takes flight, With the
promise of return. It circles
the world, It knows where to
land, Still warm in the touch, Of
a welcoming hand. Boomerang
of love, A flight never
lost, Through shadows and storms,
It still makes its course. Each time it
is cast, It will rise far
above, Returning
again, The boomerang of
love.
Return, oh, boomerang, To hearts that are
warm, To the unloved, the gentle, The
kind in the storm. And
above all, Return with the truth from
above, To restore what was given,
Return as love. Boomerang of
love, A flight never
lost, Through shadows and
storms, It still makes its
course. Each time it is cast, It
will rise far above,
Returning again, The boomerang
of love.
Through the arc of the sky, And the breath
of the
earth, Love finds the lost, And
rekindles their worth. No
force can deter, No shadow can
stay, The path of love's promise, Will
find its own way. Boomerang of
love, A flight never
lost, Through shadows and storms,
It still makes its course. Each time it
is cast, It will rise far
above, Returning
again, The boomerang of
love.
Forever it circles, Forever
it flies, Beneath the sun,
Through unending skies.
Boomerang of love, In its endless
return, The fire keeps
glowing, The hearts ever
burn.
(Upbeat music fades out)